boxofads.com 2014-02-14

# BoxofAds - Privacy Policy

## 1 Introduction

Thank you for visiting BoxOfAds.com and, if applicable, choosing to access our Services for providing you with business intelligence about competitors. This Privacy Policy, like our Terms of Service, is an integral part of using our service, and you must completely agree to it in order to use our Site and Service. 

## 2\. Definitions

Throughout this document, we may use certain words or phrases, and it is important that you understand the meaning of them. The following is a non-exhaustive list of definitions of words and phrases found in this document: 

"Agreement" means these Terms of Service;  
"BoxOfAds" refers to our company (Trade Direct), our Site, or our Service, depending on the context of the usage;  
"Service" refers to the services that we provide through our Site;  
"Site" refers to our website, [www.BoxOfAds.com](http://www.boxofads.com/);  
"User" refers to you, those who use our Services, and general visitors to our Site;  
"You" refers to you, the person who is entering into this Agreement with BoxOfAds.  

## 3\. Information Collected

Identifying Information Collected by Us 

We collect certain personal information from you when you sign up to our Services that can be used to identify you, such as your name, e-mail address, and other information. This information is disclosed only in accordance with our Terms of Service and/or this Privacy Policy. 

Information Collected by Payment Processors 

When paying us through our third party payment processor, 2Checkout.com, they may require that you submit certain information such as your name, e-mail address, address, other contact information, credit card information, or such other information as they deem appropriate. This information is not held by BoxOfAds and you should consult the third party payment processor's legal agreements to determine your privacy rights with them. You agree any disputes regarding their use of your information will be brought without naming us as a defendant. 

Non-Identifying Information 

Whenever you visit our Site, we may collect non-identifying information from you, such as your IP address, referring URL, browser, operating system, cookie information, and Internet Service Provider. Without a subpoena, voluntary compliance on the part of your Internet Service Provider, or additional records from a third party, this information alone cannot usually be used to identify you. 

## 4\. Use of Your Information

We may use your information: 

  * To process transactions.
  * To send e-mails about our Site or respond to inquiries.
  * To send e-mails about the Site and other products, news, or updates for BoxOfAds.
  * To send e-mails about other third party products or services.

##  5\. Accessing, Editing, and Removing Your Information

Users may in some cases be able to review and edit the personal information they have provided to us by logging into your account on the Site and editing their account. Although most changes may occur immediately, information may still be stored in a web browser's cache. We take no responsibility for stored information in your cache, or in other devices that may store information, and disclaim all liability of such. In addition, we may, from time to time, retain residual information about you in our backup and/or database. 

## 6\. Cookies

We use cookies for a number of purposes on our Site. For example, we use cookies to save your preferences and remember your shopping cart items. For these reasons, you must have cookies enabled in your browser to use our Site and Services. 

## 7\. Third Party Websites

BoxOfAds may post links to third party websites on its Site. Additionally, landing pages displayed through our business intelligence Services may contain third party website links. In both cases, these third party websites linked to and the landing pages themselves are not screened for privacy or security issues by us, and you release us from any liability for the conduct of these third party websites. 

Please be aware that this Privacy Policy, and any other policies in place, in addition to any amendments, does not create rights enforceable by third parties or require disclosure of any personal information relating to members of the Service or Site. BoxOfAds bears no responsibility for the information collected or used by any advertiser or third party website. Please review the privacy policy and terms of service for each site you visit through third party links, and the privacy policy and terms of service of websites displaying the landing pages that you look at. 

## 8\. Third Party Access to Your Information

Although you are entering into an Agreement with BoxOfAds to disclose your information to us, we do use third party individuals and organizations to assist us, including contractors, web hosts, and others. 

Throughout the course of our provision of our Services to you, we may delegate our authority to collect, access, use, and disseminate your information. For example, our web host stores the information that you provide us, and we may hire third parties to assist us in maintaining, repairing, improving, or otherwise assisting us with our Site and Services. 

It is therefore necessary that you grant the third parties we may use in the course of our business the same rights that you afford us under this Privacy Policy. For this reason, you hereby agree that for every authorization which you grant to us in this Privacy Policy, you also grant to any third party that we may hire, contract, or otherwise retain the services of for the purpose of operating, maintaining, repairing, or otherwise improving or preserving our website or its underlying files or systems. You agree not to hold us liable for the actions of any of these third parties, even if we would normally be held vicariously liable for their actions, and that you must take legal action against them directly should they commit any tort or other actionable wrong against you. 

## 9\. Law Enforcement

You agree that we may disclose your information to a third party where we believe, in good faith, that it is desirable to do so for the purposes of a civil action, criminal investigation, or other legal matter. In the event that we receive a subpoena affecting your privacy, we may elect to notify you to give you an opportunity to file a motion to quash the subpoena, or we may attempt to quash it ourselves, but we are not obligated to do either. We may also proactively report you and release your information without receiving any request to third parties where we believe that it is prudent to do so for legal reasons, such as instances where we believe your publications violate any law of Poland or any other country having jurisdiction over us, our Site, Services, or this Agreement. You release us from any damages that may arise from or relate to the release of your information to a request from law enforcement agencies or private litigants. 

## 10\. Commercial and Non-Commercial Communications

By providing information to the Site that forms the basis of communication with you, such as contact information, you waive all rights to file complaints concerning unsolicited email from us since, by providing such information, you agree to receive communication from us other anyone else covered under this Privacy Policy. However, you may unsubscribe from certain communications by notifying BoxOfAds that you no longer wish to receive solicitations or information and we will endeavor to remove you from the database through this "opt out" procedure. 

## 11\. Security Measures

We take certain measures to enhance the security of our Site and Services. However, we make no representations as to the security or privacy of your information. It is in our interest to keep our website secure, but we recommend that you use anti-virus software, routine credit checks, firewalls, and other precautions to protect yourself from security and privacy threats. 

## 12\. California Online Privacy Protection Act

Although located in Poland, BoxOfAds permits residents of California to use its Services and Site. Therefore, it is the intent of BoxOfAds to comply with the California Business and Professions Code §§ 22575-22579. If you are a California resident you may request certain information regarding our disclosure of personal information to any third parties for their direct marketing purposes. Various provisions throughout this Privacy Policy address requirements of the Californian privacy statutes. In summary, you must presume that we collect electronic information from all visitors. You may contact us at [admin@boxofads.com](mailto:admin@boxofads.com) with any questions. 

## 13\. International Transfer

Your information may be transferred to - and maintained on - computers located outside of your state, province, country, or other governmental jurisdiction where the privacy laws may not be as protective as those in your jurisdiction. If you are located outside Poland and choose to provide information to us, BoxOfAds transfers personal information to Poland and processes it there. Your consent to this Privacy Policy followed by your submission of such information represents your agreement to that transfer. 

## 14\. Amendments

Like our Terms of Service, we may amend this Privacy Policy from time to time. When we amend this Privacy Policy, we will place a note on our Site as to when the Privacy Policy was last modified. You must agree to the amendments as a condition of your continued use of our Site and Services. If you do not agree, you must immediately cease using our Site and Services.
